DALE LARSEN

Contact

Address

Ogden, UT, 84404

Phone

(801) 644-9624

E-mail

dale@dalelarsen.com

WWW

https://dalelarsen.com

Skills

Team Management

Project Management

Remote Work

Javascript

Angular

ReactJS

CSS/SCSS/SASS

SQL and NoSQL Databases

AWS

For all see "Technologies"

I lead, architect, manage, and build web applications and business technical solutions, and see them through to completion.

I am self-taught and have been running a web development company for over 12 years. For a showcase of projects go to https://dalelarsen.com

Work History

2017-10 -

CEO

Current

Fabuso, Ogden, UT

- After 10 years as the CTO and Senior Web Developer of Fabuso, I took the reins of the company as CEO.
- Continued to fulfill previous duties and started leading/running all the affairs of the company.

2007-11 -2017-10

CTO/Senior Full Stack Developer

Fabuso, Ogden, UT

- I worked as CTO of Fabuso and was the Senior Developer.
- Fabuso is a web development company that provides ongoing outsourced web development to its clients.
- I have overseen the acquisition of new clients and have managed our development team, developing much of the software myself.
- Each new client involved building new custom software solutions, integrating 3rd party software, and migrating old systems to the corresponding replacements.
- I know how to architect web applications, reviewing each project and choosing frameworks and solutions that best fit each one.
- I have developed these from beginning to end and beyond.

2002-09 -2005-11

Website Manager

Achieve Auto Sales, Ogden, UT

Maintained company website for car dealership. Kept up to date daily inventory on website and launched and managed eBay® listings for the cars.

Education

High school: Computer Science

Self taught. Ran my own dev company. - Ogden, UT

Technologies

Angular 2+ (3 years)

Javascript (10+ years)

React (2 years)

Jquery (10+ years)

Nodejs (4 years)

Angularis (6 years)

Java (9 years)

AWS (8 years)

CSS (10+ years)

Firebase (4 years)

MySQL (10+ years)

Web Development (10+ years)

PHP

VueJS (2 years)

ChartJS

Mocha

Gatsby

TypeScript (4 years)

Photoshop (10+ years)

Adobe XD (2 years)

Git (5 years)

Bootstrap (6 years)
APIs
User Interface (UI)
JSON
XML
GitHub
MVC
HTML5 (10+ years)
NoSQL

AJAX

SVN (10+ years)

Scrum

References

- Kurt Othmer President/CEO at EEGInfo, Inc: (818) 970-5878
- Shaye Larsen CEO/Owner at West Bridge Auto Sales, Partner at Fabuso: (801) 388-4721
- Jared Hancock Business Coach/Consultant: (801) 389-8593
- Nick Drishinski Software Developer at Rockford Fosgate: (435) 757-9991
- Michael Wilson Director, Medicare Sales at eHealth, Inc: (801) 564-0879

Projects

For a showcase of projects please go to https://dalelarsen.com